98: Hey, we’re here now!
95: Yep!
98: That was a fun ride.
Chicago: The journey isn’t over yet.
Chicago: We’re just getting started!
98: I agree.
98: Let's get going!
98: Wow!
98: This is beautiful!
7: What a picturesque!
Chicago: The train ride was really good as well!
95: I agree.
95: This is way more than Kernel!
95: I’m so glad I chose this place.
8.1: You’ve made the right decision.
OS X Tiger (10.4): Yeah, thanks for bringing us here.
95: You're all welcome!
3.1: We've still got a long way ahead.
95: Yep.
95: Shall we go eat first?
Chicago: Indeed!
95: Alright then.
Chicago: Woah!
Chicago: The biome here is so different!
98: I’ve never been to anywhere like this.
98: First impressions are great!
XP: Same here.
8.1: The desert sure does blend in!
8.1: It's also a massive area.
ME: I agree.
3.1: I agree.
95: Good question.
95: I figure we should split into groups.
Chicago: Sure.
OS X Leopard (10.5) Where do we meet?
95: Once we reach a checkpoint.
95: There should be some resting area.
Vista: This is gonna be fun!
Chicago: Yeah!
95: Alright, let's start!
95: So, how's everyone?
98: Pretty good!
Chicago: Same.
Vista: Me too.
98: My PS3 recently broke, though.
XP: Oh?
XP: What happened to it?
98: I got a Yellow Light of Death.
98: It doesn't turn on anymore, sadly.
Chicago: Ack, that's a shame.
Chicago: Is it the original model?
98: Pretty good!
Chicago: I've heard the notoriety.
Chicago: Older PS3s fail a lot quicker.
98: Sadly.
XP: Do you know a way to fix it?
98: Not really.
98: I've never fixed consoles as much.
XP: Ah, I'm sorry for that.
98: Hey, it's fine.
98: I'll just get another one.
XP: Ah, alright.
8.1: A few months here, this is the best yet!
OS X Leopard (10.5): Glad to hear.
OS X Leopard (10.5): You arrived just this year, right?
8.1: Yep.
8.1: I’ve never seen such landscapes.
8.1: Probably because I never ventured this far.
OS X Leopard (10.5): Makes sense.
8: I’ve been out on trips for a year now.
8: I gotta say, this is the best yet!
2.0: Nice to hear.
2.0: How were the trips?
8: I got it all documented.
8: I don't plan a business, though.
2.0: Ah.
Longhorn: Speaking of, this place is huge.
Longhorn: I’m pretty sure this tourism is new.
2.0: Yeah.
OS X Leopard (10.5): Looks like it.
OS X Leopard (10.5): You arrived just this year, right?
8.1: Really?
8.1: That's cool!
OS X Leopard (10.5): Agreed.
7: Some Windows systems are busy lately.
ME: I agree.
OS X Tiger (10.4): Same for us.
OS X Tiger (10.4): Only the two of us made it.
ME: Oh wow.
3.1: Are they running shops?
OS X Tiger (10.4): Pretty much.
OS X Tiger (10.4): Some of them are guarding.
3.1: Ah.
3.1: Same here.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: I used to run a market long ago.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: That was on the earth, by the way.
OS X Tiger (10.4): Oh wow, really?
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Tiger, you’ve been there before.
OS X Tiger (10.4): Wait, what?
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: How can you forget?
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: You've been there so many times!
OS X Tiger (10.4): Oh, wait.
OS X Tiger (10.4): That market!
OS X Tiger (10.4): I don’t know how I forgot that.
3.1: Haha.
95: Well, we're here!
XP: First checkpoint, it looks like?
95: Yep.
OS X Leopard (10.5): You guys arrived fast.
95: Haha.
95: That happens sometimes.
ME: Should we take a break for a bit?
ME: I’m getting exhausted.
95: Yeah, let's.
95: My CPU is throttling.
98: Same here.
95: Wow, this place is huge.
98: I can't agree more.
98: It's so different from Kernel.
Chicago: Almost like a different dimension.
98: Yeah.
98: How much have we hiked so far?
95: I figure about 400 meters.
98: Only 400 meters?!
95: Wait, I mean altitude.
98: Oh, alright.
95: I think we've travelled about 5 kilometers.
95: This is the first checkpoint, so...
98: Ah.
XP: Hikes like this are enjoyable.
Vista: Indeed.
3.1: It’s also exhausting.
3.1: But that’s the fun part.
OS X Tiger (10.4): Well said.
98: This kind of place reminds me of rallying.
98: For some reason.
Vista: Oh, right!
XP: I see that!
98: Maybe I should've brought my Gr. B.
OS X Leopard (10.5): Hey, we should have a race!
OS X Tiger (10.4): I agree.
OS X Tiger (10.4): That'd be fun.
98: Who's going to instruct, though?
ME: I'll be 98's instructor.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: And I'll be Leopard's instructor.
8.1: Hmm, I'll be one of the stewards.
2.0: I volunteer the same.
8: I think I'd rather do marshalling.
Longhorn: Same here.
98: Haha!
98: I was joking.
98: I don't even have a rally car.
95: Fair enough, haha.
95: Only a few systems sell those.
Chicago: Super expensive as well.
98: Yeah.
98: At least I get to drive one on Gran Turismo.
XP: Ah.
XP: That's more affordable.
98: Much more.
95: Hey guys, by the way.
95: We're making good progress.
XP: Yep.
XP: What's our aim?
95: I figure at least 700 meters of altitude.
95: As well as a 15-kilometer round trip.
XP: Pretty good!
Chicago: Sounds good!
98: Yeah, I'm ready now.
98: Should we resume?
95: Yeah, let's.
OS X Leopard (10.5): We're ready as well.
3.1: Same here.
3.1: Also, are we staying in groups?
95: Preferably.
95: It's difficult coordinating.
3.1: Alright.
95: Alright, let's resume!
98: Checkpoint 3!
Vista: No way...
Vista: We're half-way through now!
ME: After all the hard work...
ME: That was eventful!
98: I know right!
7: I agree.
7: Also, it's already sunset.
95: Oh, yeah.
95: Let's stop the hike here.
95: For today, that is.
98: Good idea.
98: Should we settle here or?
95: Yeah, let's go scout around.
98: Alright.
XP: It's getting darker.
98: Yeah.
95: We better settle fast.
95: We won't be able to see anything.
98: Wait, that looks like a good spot.
95: Ah, I see it!
98: Should we go there?
95: Yep, sounds good!
95: Alright!
95: Let’s get things working.
98: I can help set up the tents.
95: Sure thing!
Chicago: Should I help with the campfire?
95: Much appreciated.
Chicago: Alright.
95: I figure we settle in the cave.
95: Just for some good measure.
98: Good idea.
95: Alright, let's get started!
98: Alright, I'll go get the tent bags.
95: Sure.
95: Alright, you guys can settle.
98: This is really a new experience.
8.1: I know right!
Vista: Lots of fun today.
Vista: As well as a unique adventure.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: I agree.
Longhorn: How much did we hike?
98: Hmm, 95?
95: We’ve done way more than our goal.
95: We've hiked about 12 kilometers.
OS X Leopard (10.5): Are you serious?
OS X Leopard (10.5): I'm surprised I even made it.
95: Me too.
98: Yeah, my battery is running very low.
98: About time for a recharge.
98: Wait, what's the total round trip distance?
95: I think it was 20 kilometers.
98: Wow.
98: Good work, team!
XP: Thanks, 98!
OS X Leopard (10.5): You too!
Chicago: Wow, it's already dark.
Longhorn: I know right.
95: After all the adventures and chaos?
Longhorn: Haha.
98: We're already on the sequel!
98: Oh well.
Chicago: What an adventure, should I say?
98: Can't agree more.
98: Also, I’ve got a surprise.
95: Oh?
98: I got something just right for the campfire.
Chicago: What is it?
98: Well, I've got some shrimp.
98: We can grill them!
8.1: Wow, really?
8.1: Awesome stuff!
95: That’s the best you can have!
98: Yep!
98: I have tons of them in my food folder.
98: Anyone wants some?
Vista: I’ll take some!
XP: Me too.
95: Welp, before we start eating…
95: Let's pray first.
8.1: Ah, right.
95: Lord Gates, thanks for the food today.
95: We pray that you’ll give us a blessed time.
8.1: A blessed time and food.
Longhorn: Thanks for everything you’ve done.
98: All that you’ve done for us.
98: This is our prayer to you.
95: Amen!
98: Alright, let's begin!
98: That was a great meal.
7: I can't agree more.
8.1: Thanks for the shrimps, 98.
98: You’re all welcome!
Chicago: I figure we should get some rest.
Chicago: Tomorrow’s another long day as well.
95: Yeah.
95: There's still some smoke here.
95: The fans worked really well with that.
Chicago: Haha.
95: Alright then, let's recharge overnight.
95: Goodnight everyone!
Memphis: Welp, we’ve finished!
2000: Great!
2000: I agree.
OS X Snow Leopard (10.6): Too bad I couldn't join the trip.
3.0: Me too.
2000: We've got a job to do, though.
3.0: Yeah.
3.0: Not just for our shops.
Ubuntu 18.04: Haha.
2000: Well, this room is set!
2000: I think we've done a great job.
Home Server 2011: Agreed.
Home Server 2011: Are they coming back today?
2000: Yep.
2000: Just in time.
2000: Anyway, let's go.
2000: So, are you guys excited?
Memphis: Of course!
Ubuntu 18.04: Yep.
Home Server 2011: Hard to imagine it’s been this long.
Home Server 2011: 25 years is unbelievable.
2000: Me neither.
OS X Mavericks (10.9): I know right.
OS X Mavericks (10.9): I’m looking forward to this!
OS X Snow Leopard (10.6): Oh yeah, what’d you guys get?
3.0: I got him a NT 3.51 disc.
3.0: He's a collector, so...
OS X Mavericks (10.9): Cool!
OS X Mavericks (10.9): I got him a Wii game.
2000: Oh wow.
2000: What is it?
OS X Mavericks (10.9): I’m looking forward to this!
OS X Snow Leopard (10.6): I think he’ll appreciate that.
2000: That’s a nice gift.
Ubuntu 18.04: I got him a Roland SC-88.
2000: Woah.
2000: How did you find one?
Ubuntu 18.04: Yeah, about that.
Ubuntu 18.04: I had to go pretty far.
2000: Good dedication!
Ubuntu 18.04: Thanks.
Home Server 2011: I got him the original Xbox.
Home Server 2011: He seems interested in consoles.
2000: Yeah, he is.
2000: I got him something opposite.
Home Server 2011: Oh?
OS X Mavericks (10.9): What did you buy?
2000: Well, I did this with the others.
2000: I got him some Gran Turismo games.
OS X Mavericks (10.9): Oh, wow.
OS X Mavericks (10.9): That’s pretty good timing.
2000: How come?
OS X Mavericks (10.9): He told me his PS3 had faults.
2000: Wait, what?
2000: How come?
2000: I hope this console compensates for that.
OS X Mavericks (10.9): Yep, it should!
OS X Snow Leopard (10.6): I just noticed, it’s already afternoon.
2000: Oh wow.
2000: I still need to get some food for the party.
3.0: He's a collector, so...
OS X Mavericks (10.9): I can help.
OS X Snow Leopard (10.6): Same here.
3.0: Me too.
2000: Thanks, everyone!
2000: Let’s get to work, then.
2000: Should we start with the groceries or?
3.0: We can start with that.
OS X Mavericks (10.9): Yep.
2000: Alright.
95: We're home!
98: Woohoo!
98: That was really fun.
XP: Again, thanks for the trip!
XP: It was wonderful!
95: My pleasure, everyone!
95: Actually, it's not over yet.
98: Wait, what?
95: Haha.
95: There’s a surprise waiting for you, 98.
95: Everyone, follow me!
Home Server 2011: Welcome home, everyone!
95: Hello, Server 2011!
Home Server 2011: I hope you all enjoyed your trip!
Home Server 2011: We prepared something crazy.
98: Wait, is today something special?
95: You'll see!
95: Should we go in now?
Home Server 2011: Yep, we're ready!
98: Wait, what?!
98: It's my birthday today?!
95: Ah, yes it is!
XP: It’s June 25!
98: I'm going to faint.
98: How did I forget my own anniversary?
95: Haha!
95: No clue.
98: I'm speechless, everyone.
98: Thank you all so much!
95: All good, 98!
95: Thanks for everything as well!
98: Mutually welcome!
Home Server 2011: 2000 prepared a dinner for us.
Home Server 2011: It should be ready now.
95: Alright, let's go eat then!
98: What...
98: There's so many gifts!
95: Don’t be intimidated.
95: But yeah, it's a lot.
98: Thanks so much, everyone!
Chicago: More than welcome, 98!
2000: Yeah, no problem!
95: You can go ahead and check each of ours.
95: Preferably mine first...
Chicago: Oh no you don't, sir!
95: Just kidding.
98: Let me check the PS3.
98: Wait a second...
98: This is such a coincidence.
2000: Haha, I thought!
98: Who bought this?
2000: That one's from me, XP, and Vista.
98: Wow, thanks guys.
98: My PS3 has a YLoD now.
98: I think this will replace it.
Vista: Good to hear!
2000: By the way, this has backwards compatibility.
98: Wait, for the PlayStation 2?
2000: Yep.
98: You are joking.
98: That’s the one I was looking for!
98: And thanks for all the Gran Turismo games!
2000: No problem!
2000: Thank IE as well.
2000: We bought those from him.
98: I’ll be sure to thank him.
Chicago: What a gift!
98: I know right!
98: Let me check the next gift.
98: Ah, I remember this game.
98: I used to play this on the earth.
95: That one’s from me!
98: Thanks, 95!
98: I’m looking forward for a revisit.
98: This will be pretty fun!
95: You’re welcome!
98: Let’s check the other gifts.
98: Wow, that was a ton of stuff.
Chicago: I know right.
98: Most of the gifts are maniacal.
98: You guys got it all spot-on.
OS X Leopard (10.5): I glad you liked our gifts!
2.0: Yeah, very.
98: This is the best birthday ever.
2000: Glad to hear that!
XP: Yep.
95: Hey, we’ve still got one thing left to do.
95: I’m assuming you guys know why we’re here.
95: I brought my projector for a movie watch!
98: Cool! What are we watching?
95: After all the trials and tribulations...
95: I got a copy of 7's Final Days Season 1
Chicago: Wait, what?!
98: I might faint anytime soon.
98: I never expected any of this...
98: All this means a lot to me.
7: We're all glad, 98.
95: After all, we went through tons of things.
95: It's good to offer something back.
98: Thank you, 95.
95: No problem!
XP: Shall we start the video now?
98: Definitely!
98: I can't wait to watch this.
95: Alright, we shall begin watching!
98: Windows Vista Production?
Vista: Hey, that's me!
98: Sounds like you made this!
Vista: Don't spoil it!
98: Haha!
Vista: (I did not make this, by the way).
Chicago: Oh no, it's Tux!
Chicago: Hahaha!
98: Memory leaks, perhaps.
Chicago: Indeed.
95: After all, we went through tons of things.
Chicago: Oh no.
Chicago: Not Assembly!
7: Hey, that's me!
7: Why do I look like I have a fatigue?
98: 7, did you forget?
7: Oh wait... Right.
OS X Leopard (10.5): I think this is months before January 2020.
98: Yeah, I think so.
98: Costa's a nice name.
Longhorn: Reminds me of my coffeeshop.
Longhorn: All those years back!
2000: It's been a while since I drank coffee.
98: Same here.
98: What is Linux Mint doing?
Chicago: I hope he's not up to something.
7: I definitely hope not!
XP: I like the building design.
ME: Looks pretty contemporary.
OS X Mavericks (10.9): Hey, that's me!
98: This is oddly similar to Longhorn's coffeeshop...
98: Wait a second!
98: This is literally Longhorn's coffeeshop!
2000: Haha, it's the same design!
2000: I wonder if they copied ours...
98: Haha!
7: Wise words, 10.
98: I agree.
ME: Reminds me of my life back then.
ME: I'm glad that's over with.
98: Wow, this car is cool.
98: This engine sounds crazy.
7: I like the logo interface.
7: It must've sucked being this unwell.
Vista: Oh no...
Chicago: I knew it!
95: I hope he'll be alright.
7: Go, other 7!
95: Come on, you can do this!
Chicago: Keep the resilience!
7: Agh!
95: Ouch.
Chicago: Come on!!
7: OW!
ME: WHAT IS THIS?!
Chicago: TURN DOWN THE VOLUME!!!
95: AAAAAAAAA
98: WAIT, NO!
7: Noo, he's so ill.
95: I feel so bad.
95: Near EOL and yet dealing with this...
XP: What is Chrome OS even doing?
Chicago: The disguise is going all over the place.
Vista: Windows Earth.
Chicago: What is going on with his invention?
98: It's going to explode!
98: Wow, that was magnificent!
95: Absolutely amazing.
7: A unique adventure of its own, really.
7: I'm moved!
2000: Me too.
98: I think we all are!
98: Thanks again for all this, 95!
95: You're very welcome!
OS X Mavericks (10.9): An hour well spent!
Chicago: Let's not forget Chrome OS though...
98: Indeed.
95: Wow, it's already night.
95: I suggest we get going.
98: Alright then.
98: Au revoir, everyone!